Yes, I stocked up on some tools and medicines I can use.
Thank you very much.
Sakamoto, do you doubt me?
You can't survive here without mutual trust.
Okay, hold on to this on the way back.
It has important materials inside.
Be careful with it.
I-I will.
Wh-Why's he... so intimidating?
The first one to move wins.
Stay on the defensive, and you'll lose your chance.
Ryouta, that is the only difference between us,
regardless of whether you can understand that.
Now, let's hurry.
Ryouta!
Ryouta, get rid of the trunk!
Hurry! Throw it away!
The trunk's got a BIM...
There's a bomb inside it!
Ryouta!
One down!
All the way from the farthest ends of the world
saihate no story idaite
I have been wandering without a destination
ate mo naku samayoitsuzuketa
Now a new world emerges from the haze
nijinda new world
The game has only just begun
The beginning of the end is in my eyes
ima hajimari no eyes
This is where tomorrow brings a new game
It's time to learn that pain is gain
Ready fight
To squash my past despair
kako no shitsubou nuritsubusu tame ni
I've had to sacrifice my future
gisei ni shite kita mirai
Until my life expires
boku no life ga tsukiru made
I'll keep fighting my fate
sono sadame buchikowashiteiku no sa
Ah, break out and start a revolution
Searching for the exact answer
hitotsu no kotae wo sagashite
I challenge myself to an extreme race
genkai no race ni idonde
I know it's my only chance
ichidokiri no chansu to shitte
I'll overcome my preordained fate
seotta unmei koeteikun da yo
All the way from the farthest ends of the world
saihate no story idaite
I have been wandering without a destination
ate mo naku samayoitsuzuketa
Now a new world emerges from the haze
nijinda new world
The game has only just begun
the game has only just begun
The beginning of the end is in my eyes
ima hajimari no eyes
Ryouta...
Ryouta!
No!
Your boyfriend's dead.
I have lots more BIMs now.
But more importantly...
How did you figure out a BIM was in the trunk?
I actually wanted you both dead.
Well, whatever.
The results won't change.
The weak exist to be devoured by the strong.
That's true in any endeavor.
I'm going to survive and get off this island again.
You're going to help pave my way.
Pave my way... with your corpse!
You haven't changed at all, Dr. Date.
Th-That voice...
Sh-Shiki?!
Revival
Murasaki Shiki!
10 Minutes Earlier
The medicine supply?
Yes. A giant lizard bit one of our companions.
I think he's poisoned.
He won't stop bleeding.
So, I was hoping we'd find some kind of serum.
I'm afraid to say...
There's nothing like that here.
That can't be...
But there are painkillers and antibiotics.
Come with me.
I'll show you the way.
Three of us are here.
But I don't trust one of them.
Then, why are you with them?
W-Well...
The medicine is in the room through that window.
Mr. Date.
That's the man we're...
Th-That's definitely him.
That's Dr. Date!
Why is he on this island again?
What's wrong?!
Are you okay?
That's him.
The one who did this to me...
Date Masahito.
It was that man.
That's him? Mr. Date did that?
He's the one who betrayed Ms. Murasaki to escape this island?
What kind of BIMs does he have right now?
The remote controlled type.
Remote controlled...
Listen, there's no doubt that he'll betray you.
The only question is when.
Ryouta...
No!
He's planted a remote controlled BIM in that trunk for sure.
He's used that trick before.
I'm sure of it.
Himiko!
No, Ryouta!
Ryouta, get rid of the trunk!
Hurry! Throw it away!
The trunk's got a BIM...
There's a bomb inside it!
Himiko!
What are you doing, Himiko?
Ryouta...
Ryouta was...
Stand up.
We have to run!
So you're still alive, Shiki.
Ryouta... Ryouta...
Pull yourself together!
It doesn't matter where you run.
I've already planted BIMs.
Like this one!
He planted BIMs ahead of time.
They're probably all over this building.
We're going outside.
Come on. Over here.
Looks like my timing was off.
Been a while, hasn't it, Shiki?
I never thought you'd still be alive.
Did you patch up your missing arm yourself?
That took guts.
Let me applaud you.
And I never thought I'd see you back here.
You made it out once,
but you must've pissed someone off again.
I'd pity you if it weren't so funny.
What did you say, you bitch?
You probably planted your remote controlled bombs all over this area, right?
I decided I'd make my stand here.
So I placed all my remote controlled bombs in this area.
I know exactly where each BIM is.
If you try to run, I'll definitely kill you this time!
What's wrong?
Is the little girl all ready to give up?
I guess I can understand.
Her boyfriend was killed right in front of her.
Don't worry.
You'll be seeing him soon.
Thanks to his BIMs.
I won't let that happen!
You let your guard down!
If she presses the switch,
I can fight, too!
Now it's two against one.
I wonder who's at the disadvantage here.
I never forgot you... not for an instant.
Back then, I cursed myself.
I was a fool.
I was ignorant.
And I was stupid enough
to put my faith in love.
Don't you think God must have brought us together again?
S-Stay away.
Keep away from me!
Stop right there!
You fell for it.
Th-The other side of the wall?
No!
You should've stayed dead the first time.
Now, the only one left is that stupid school girl who can't fight.
Once I kill her, I'll take their two chips,
plus the three they collected.
Head back, kill the cripple, and I'll have six.
That's all I need.
This is too easy.
He's coming.
He's coming for me.
I have to run.
Oh, right.
I'm surrounded by BIMs.
I have to fight.
But I'm on my own. How can I?
I'm going... to die here.
And just when I'd started to think I actually didn't want to...
and that I was ready to give it my all.
Without Ryouta...
Without Ryouta here...
When I was fed up with reality and escaped to the world of the game,
he always cheered me up.
He's always been there for me.
If I'd known...
If I'd known this was going to happen...
I should've just told him I was Himiko!
Himiko, was it?
I'll give you one last chance.
Will you join me?
I'm a veteran.
We can get all the chips we need and go home.
Well?
Doesn't sound so bad, does it?
Liar!
That's how you deceived Ms. Murasaki!
I see.
So you know...
Then, just die!
This is for the best.
At least I can die... with dignity.
Farewell, Mother.
Why?!
Why won't it explode?!
The detonator won't activate.
Does that mean I don't have the right to use it?
What's going on?
H-He's...
He's...
still alive?
That's what it was, Mr. Date?
Good God, you're low.
Are you okay, Himiko?
R-Ryouta?
H-How?
How did you survive that?!
5 Minutes Earlier
Ryouta, get rid of the trunk!
Hurry! Throw it away!
The trunk's got a BIM...
There's a bomb inside it!
R-Ryouta, I...
I thought you were dead.
Yeah.
For a minute, so did I.
It almost feels like something is keeping me alive.
I've learned my lesson now.
What has died, is my naïvety.
Mr. Date...
No... Date!
As long as I'm alive, the only BIMs you can use are your remote controlled type.
And you've planted all of them in this area.
But that means that, right now, you're totally unarmed.
I've got one BIM, a cracker,
and Himiko is fully armed.
This fight is over.
Give up and admit defeat.
Or...
Or I'll kill you right here!
Wait... Wait, Date!
Stay away!
Let me go!
I can't believe he's not dead!
I should've made sure.
Crap! Crap!
That's right, come on!
Come after me!
I'm unarmed.
You have the advantage.
You can't lose.
That's it.
Just relax...
Lower your guard.
Chase me as I run!
Date!
Dumbass!
I hid a BIM under those boards.
I'll show you what a veteran is capable of.
Die!
What?
While you were chasing Himiko, I found a BIM that you set
in the only place nearby to hide one.
So, I moved it.
R-Ryouta!
Ryouta, what will you do with him?
We have to kill him.
He kept trying to kill me until the very end.
He only got close to us because he wanted our chips.
We can't stay with him.
And look at him.
He won't survive on this island.
Wait.
Ms. Murasaki!
You survived?!
Don't just kill me off like that.
I'm fine, as you can see.
You don't need to dirty your hands.
This was always between the two of us.
Shiki...
H-Help... me...
Sh-Shiki...
You're pathetic.
At least die like a man.
You've always been this way, looking down on people... using them...
Tossing them aside like garbage when they outlived their usefulness.
You're dishonest.
You're a disgusting man!
I'll give you your judgment.
I-I'm sorry.
Stop that.
Just stop it.
Don't look at me.
Don't look at me like that!
It's just not fair...
Y-You'll forgive me?
I'll never forgive you.
Not someone like you!
I can't...
There's no way I can...
No peeking, okay?
I know that.
You're just there as my bodyguard.
I know that, too.
But you know, I don't get it.
Get what?
Ms. Murasaki.
Didn't he do something terrible to her in the last game?
Even so, she saved him.
I don't understand how adults think.
Ryouta, aren't you an adult?
Maybe I never grew up because I was a NEET.
I think... that I understand.
Really?
Just a little, though.
Just a little.
Maybe you have to be a woman to understand.
Maybe so.
We have to get the medicine Ms. Murasaki gave us to Mr. Taira.
Himiko, I've got a suggestion.
What?
I want to pick up some chips on our way back.
We've seen bodies here that we haven't checked for chips, right?
That Akechi guy who attacked you.
The father of that crazy kid I met.
And the guy with the buzz cut I fought at the start.
I want to get them before anyone else.
But with the ones we have, that will only give us six.
We'll still be one short.
That first guy I saw had two BIM pouches.
Which means he should have two chips.
That would make seven.
We could use them to bring a helicopter.
We hijack the helicopter, and everyone gets off the island!
We won't have to fight anymore.
Yeah.
We won't have to kill anyone, will we?
That's right!
Ryouta, you perv!
Jerk! Pervert!
Y-You're the one who came out of the shower!
You Peeping Tom!
I knew I couldn't trust men!
I hold my breath and close my eyes
iki wo sezu me wo fuseta
The sky is glittering so brightly
hikyou na hodo kirameku aozora ga
Coloring the space over our heads
kono machi no zujou wo color
I can't stop shedding tears
tomedonaku namida furaseru kara
I can't just push it aside as memories
omoide ni wa dekinai
Just seeing you made me so happy
au dake de ureshikatta
I didn't understand you
kimi no koto shirazu ni
And hurt you
kizutsukete
Nobody knows
nobody knows
You don't have to give me another chance
gomen ne watashi wo mou
Just forget about me
yurusanaide wasurete
No good. There's no chip here, either.
Someone's taken it.
We checked all three, and to think there's none...
What's wrong?
Are you thinking about that Akechi guy?
If you're blaming yourself, I don't think you should.
It was self-defense.
You were dragged to this island and forced to play this weird game.
It isn't your fault.
It's the fault of those behind this.
And his, for losing control of himself!
Let's head back.
Yeah.
This doesn't make sense.
Once or twice would mean another player had stumbled upon the body...
but all three?
The only one who knew about that chip was...
No way. That can't be.
No, it couldn't be...
Seems to me like you're satisfied with holding yourself back.
To me, you're like a gullible little kid.
I stopped being like that!
We're all going to survive this.
And we'll leave the island together.
Won't we, Mr. Taira?
Look at this fog.
I'm glad we made it back.
I wonder if Mr. Taira's worried.
What's wrong?
Shh.
I hear something.
That sound...
A homing type?
Ryouta!
The only person with this type of BIM...
It can't be!
Can't tell where we'll go back to...
...or what'll happen in the future.
Even so, you were there...
...there for me.
You are hope...
...my hope.
And in this hellish place...
...we'll survive, together.
Final
Episode
Bonds
Final
Episode
Bonds